Guide to the New American Library Archive 1943-1962 MSS.070
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: New American Library, Editorial/Author Files
  - Post, Charles J., "The Little War of Private Post,", 1958-1961 (Box 62, Folder 1455)
  - Post, Charles J., "The Little War of Private Post," ms. and artwork, undated (Box 62, Folder 1456)
  - Powell, Lawrence, "The Rough Riders,", 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 1457)
  - Prabhavananda, Swami, and Frederick Manchester, "The Upanishads,", 1956-1960 (Box 62, Folder 1458)
  - Pratolini, Vasco, "A Hero of Our Time,", 1950-1953 (Box 62, Folder 1459)
  - Pratolini, Vasco, "Naked Streets,", 1952-1959 (Box 62, Folder 1460)
  - Pratolini, Vasco, "A Tale of Poor Lovers,", 1949-1961 (Box 62, Folder 1461)
  - Pratt, Rex, "You Tell My Son,", 1956-1959 (Box 63, Folder 1462)
  - Pratt, Theodore, general correspondence, 1949-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1463)
  - Pratt, Theodore, "Thunder Mountain,", 1949-1955 (Box 63, Folder 1464)
  - Presser, Jacob, general correspondence, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 1465)
  - Price, Lucien, general correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 63, Folder 1466)
  - Pritchett, V.S., "The Private Papers of Henry Ryecroft,", 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1467)
  - Prokosh, Frederic, "The Asiatics,", 1960 (Box 63, Folder 1468)
  - Pushkin, Alexander, "The Captain's Daughter and Other Tales,", 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1469)
  - Radiguet, Raymond, "The Devil in the Flesh,", 1949-1960 (Box 63, Folder 1470)
  - Raine, William MacLeod, general correspondence, 1948-1953 (Box 63, Folder 1471)
  - Raine, William MacLeod, "Clattering Hoofs,", 1949-1957 (Box 63, Folder 1472)
  - Raine, William MacLeod, "Fighting Tenderfoot,", 1948-1951 (Box 63, Folder 1473)
  - Raine, William MacLeod, "Guns of the Frontiers,", 1953-1960 (Box 63, Folder 1474)
  - Raine, William MacLeod, "Justice Comes to Tomahawk,", 1952-1954 (Box 63, Folder 1475)
  - Raine, William MacLeod, "Powdersmoke Feud,", 1949-1957 (Box 63, Folder 1476)
  - Raine, William MacLeod, "Six-Gun Kid,", 1951-1956 (Box 63, Folder 1477)
  - Raine, William MacLeod, "Sons of the Saddle,", 1948-1960 (Box 63, Folder 1478)
  - Ramati, Alexander, "Rebel Against the Light,", 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1479)
  - Rapport, Samuel, and Helen Wright, "The Crust of the Earth,", 1953-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1480)
  - Rapport, Samuel, and Helen Wright, "The Story of Sex,", 1952-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1481)
  - Rattigan, Terence, "The Prince and the Showgirl,", 1957-1960 (Box 63, Folder 1482)
  - Rattigan, Terence, "Ross,", 1960 (Box 63, Folder 1483)
  - Rattigan, Terence, "Separate Tables,", 1956-1959 (Box 63, Folder 1484)
  - Rawson, Tabor, "I Want to Live,", 1958-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1485)
  - Ray, Wesley, "Damaron's Gun,", 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 1486)
  - Rayner, William, "Gourmet Cooking by the Clock,", 1961 (Box 63, Folder 1487)
  - Reed, Henry Hope, Jr., and Christopher Tunnard, "American Skyline,", 1956-1958 (Box 63, Folder 1488)
  - Reeves, James, "The Holy Bible in Brief,", 1953-1956 (Box 63, Folder 1489)
  - Regents of the University of California, "Visual Arts and Music,", 1955 (Box 63, Folder 1490)
  - Reid, Ed, "The Mafia,", 1951-1959 (Box 63, Folder 1491)
  - Reik, Theodore, "Sex in Man and Woman,", 1960 (Box 63, Folder 1492)
  - Reinhardt, Guenther, "Crime Without Punishment,", 1952-1956 (Box 63, Folder 1493)
  - Remarque, Erich Maria, "Arch of Triumph,", 1950-1958 (Box 63, Folder 1494)
  - Remarque, Erich Maria, "Spark of Life,", 1951-1956 (Box 63, Folder 1495)
  - Richards, Sylivia, "San Fernando Valley,", 1960 (Box 63, Folder 1496)
  - Richmond, Roe, "The Tall Man,", 1960 (Box 63, Folder 1497)
  - Ridgway, Jason, "West Side Jungle,", 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 1498)
  - Rivette, Marc, "The Incident,", 1956-1960 (Box 63, Folder 1499)
  - Roberts, Elizabeth, "The Great Meadow,", 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1500)
  - Roberts, Elizabeth, "The Time of Man,", 1952-1955 (Box 63, Folder 1501)
  - Roberts, Henry L., "Russia and America,", 1956-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1502)
  - Robertson, Frank, "Rawhide,", 1960 (Box 63, Folder 1503)
  - Robertson, Frank, "This Man Dawson,", 1960 (Box 63, Folder 1504)
  - Robertson, Frank, "Wanted Dead or Alive,", 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1505)
  - Robinson, David, "The Confessions of Alma Quarter,", 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1506)
  - Robinson, Marie, "The Power of Sexual Surrender,", 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1507)
  - Roche, Paul, general correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1508)
  - Roche, Paul, memos, reports, reading file, 1956-1959 (Box 63, Folder 1509)
  - Roche, Paul, Aeschylus translations, 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1510)
  - Roche, Paul, "The Oedipus Plays of Sophocles,", 1948-1959 (Box 63, Folder 1511)
  - Roche, Paul, manuscripts, undated (Box 63, Folder 1512)
  - Roche, Paul, "Vessel of Dishonour,", 1958-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1513)
  - Roddman, Philip, "Keys to Literature,", 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 1514)
  - Rodman, Selden, general correspondence, 1947-1961 (Box 63, Folder 1515)
  - Rodman, Selden, "100 American Poems,", 1945-1960 (Box 63, Folder 1516)
  - Rodman, Selden, "100 American Poems,", 1946-1960 (Box 63, Folder 1517)
  - Rogers, Matilda, "Flower Arrangements Anyone Can Do Anywhere,", 1953-1961 (Box 64, Folder 1518)
  - Rolvaag, Ole, "Giants in the Earth,", 1957-1958 (Box 64, Folder 1519)
  - Romains, Jules, "Death of a Nobody,", 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 1520)
  - Roman, Lawrence, "Powder Keg,", 1958-1959 (Box 64, Folder 1521)
  - Rooke, Daphne, "Grove of Fever Trees,", 1951-1957 (Box 64, Folder 1522)
  - Rooke, Daphne, "Mittee,", 1951-1953 (Box 64, Folder 1523)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, "Rough Riders,", 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 1524)
  - Roscoe, Mike [pseud. John Roscoe and Michael Ruso], general correspondence, 1951-1960 (Box 64, Folder 1525)
  - Roscoe, Mike [pseud. John Roscoe and Michael Ruso], "Death is a Round Black Ball", undated (Box 64, Folder 1526)
  - Roscoe, Mike [pseud. John Roscoe and Michael Ruso], "Everybody Dies,", 1952-1960 (Box 64, Folder 1527)
  - Roscoe, Mike [pseud. John Roscoe and Michael Ruso], "One Tear For My Grave,", 1955-1958 (Box 64, Folder 1528)
  - Roscoe, Mike [pseud. John Roscoe and Michael Ruso], "Riddle Me This,", 1952-1953 (Box 64, Folder 1529)
  - Roscoe, Mike [pseud. John Roscoe and Michael Ruso], "Slice of Hell,", 1953-1955 (Box 64, Folder 1530)
  - Rosenthal, Raymond, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 1531)
  - Roshwald, Mordecai, "Level 7,", 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 1532)
  - Roskolenko, Harry, "Conga II,", 1960-1961 (Box 64, Folder 1533)
  - Ross, James, "They Don't Dance Much,", 1951-1960 (Box 64, Folder 1534)
  - Ross, Sam, "The Tight Corner,", 1956-1960 (Box 64, Folder 1535)
  - Ross, Walter, "Diet to Suit Yourself,", 1953-1959 (Box 64, Folder 1536)
  - Rossi, Jean-Baptiste, "The Awakening,", 1951-1958 (Box 65, Folder 1537)
  - Rossiter, Clinton, "The American Presidency,", 1955-1960 (Box 65, Folder 1538)
  - Rossiter, Clinton, "The Federalist Papers,", 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 1539)
  - Rosten, Leo, general correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 65, Folder 1540)
  - Rostow, W.W., et. al., "The Dynamics of Soviet Society,", 1952-1960 (Box 65, Folder 1541)
  - Rothenberg, Robert, "Medical Dictionary,", 1961 (Box 65, Folder 1542)
  - Rouse, W.H.D., general correspondence, 1947-1961 (Box 65, Folder 1543)
  - Rouse, W.H.D., "Gods, Heroes, and Men of Ancient Greece,", 1956-1958 (Box 65, Folder 1544)
  - Rouse, W.H.D., "Iliad" [Homer], 1948-1961 (Box 65, Folder 1545)
  - Rouse, W.H.D., "Plato" [1], 1950-1954 (Box 65, Folder 1546)
  - Rouse, W.H.D., "Plato" [2], 1955-1956 (Box 65, Folder 1547)
  - Rouse, W.H.D., "Plato" [3], 1957-1959 (Box 65, Folder 1548)
  - Rouse, W.H.D., "The Story of Odysseus,", 1947-1960 (Box 65, Folder 1549)
  - Rouse, W.H.D., 'Xenophon,", 1957-1963 (Box 65, Folder 1550)
  - Rowe, Colin, general correspondence, 1959 (Box 65, Folder 1551)
  - Roy, Jules, "The Navigator,", 1955-1956 (Box 65, Folder 1552)
  - Roy, Jules, "The Unfaithful Wife,", 1956-1957 (Box 65, Folder 1553)
  - Rugoff, Milton, "Marco Polo,", 1961 (Box 65, Folder 1554)
  - Runbeck, Margaret Lee, "Time for Love,", 1950-1959 (Box 65, Folder 1555)
  - Ruso, Michael [pseud. Mike Roscoe], general correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 65, Folder 1556)
  - Russ, Martin, "The Last Parallel,", 1956-1959 (Box 65, Folder 1557)
  - Russell, Bertrand, "The ABC of Relativity,", 1949-1960 (Box 65, Folder 1558)
  - Russell, Bertrand, 'The Conquest of Happiness,", 1949-1958 (Box 65, Folder 1559)
  - Russell, Bertrand, "Our Knowledge of the External World,", 1960 (Box 65, Folder 1560)
  - Russell, William, "A Wind is Rising,", 1950-1956 (Box 65, Folder 1561)
  - St. Exupery, Antoine de, "Night Flight,", 1956-1960 (Box 65, Folder 1562)
  - St. George, George, and Rudy Mate, "Thermopylae,", 1960 (Box 65, Folder 1563)
  - St. Johns, Adela, "The Platinum Blond,", 1957-1959 (Box 65, Folder 1564)
  - St. Leger, David, "A Treasury of Wisdom and Inspiration,", 1950-1957 (Box 65, Folder 1565)
  - Salinger, J.D., "The Catcher in the Rye,", 1951-1961 (Box 65, Folder 1566)
  - Salinger, J.D., "Nine Stories,", 1951-1961 (Box 65, Folder 1567)
  - Saltykov-Schedrin, M., "The Golovlevs,", 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 1568)
  - Sanderson, Ivan T., "How to Know the American Mammals,", 1946-1951 (Box 65, Folder 1569)
  - Sanderson, Ivan T., "How to Know the American Mammals,", 1952-1959 (Box 65, Folder 1570)
  - Sanderson, Ivan T., "How to Know the Reptiles and Amphibians,", 1951-1956 (Box 65, Folder 1571)
  - Sanford, John B., "The Hard Guys,", 1955-1960 (Box 65, Folder 1572)
  - Saroyan, William, general correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box 65, Folder 1573)
  - Saroyan, William, "Rock Wagram,", 1951-1953 (Box 65, Folder 1574)
  - Savage, Thomas, "Lona Hanson,", 1948-1951 (Box 65, Folder 1575)
  - Savoy, Willard, "Alien Land,", 1949-1950 (Box 65, Folder 1576)
  - Sawyer, W.W., "Mathematician's Delight,", 1946-1947 (Box 65, Folder 1577)
  - Scarlett, Bishop William, "The Christian Demand for Social Justice,", 1948-1959 (Box 65, Folder 1578)
  - Scarlett, Bishop William, "Christianity Takes a Stand,", 1945-1957 (Box 65, Folder 1579)
  - Scarlett, Bishop William, "Christianity Takes a Stand", undated (Box 65, Folder 1580)
  - Schaefer, Jack, "Company of Cowards,", 1957-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1581)
  - Schary, Dore, "Sunrise at Campobello,", 1958-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1582)
  - Scheer, George F., and Hugh F. Rankin, "Rebels and Redcoats,", 1956-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1583)
  - Schiff, Pearl, "Scollay Square,", 1952-1955 (Box 66, Folder 1584)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Jr., "The Age of Jackson,", 1948-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1585)
  - Schmitt, Gladys, "Confessions of the Name,", 1952-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1586)
  - Schonfield, Hugh J., general correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1587)
  - Schonfield, Hugh J., "The Bible: Its Books and Background,", 1956-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1588)
  - Schonfield, Hugh J., "The New Testament,", 1956-1959 (Box 66, Folder 1589)
  - Schonfield, Hugh J., "Reader's Companion to Biblical Literature,", 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1590)
  - Schonfield, Hugh J., "Song of Songs,", 1957-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1591)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, "Out of My Life and Thought,", 1948-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1592)
  - Scott, Paul, "Love Pavilion,", 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1593)
  - Sedillot, Rene, "The History of the World,", 1951-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1594)
  - Sell, Henry B., general correspondence, 1954-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1595)
  - Seltzer, Charles A.., "Son of Arizona,", 1948-1949 (Box 66, Folder 1596)
  - Serguine, Jacques, "Special People,", 1960 (Box 66, Folder 1597)
  - Shannon, Jimmy, "The Devil's Passkey,", 1952-1957 (Box 66, Folder 1598)
  - Shapiro, Charles, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 1599)
  - Shapley, Harlow, "Science Ponders Religion,", 1960 (Box 66, Folder 1600)
  - Shaw, Arnold, "The Money Song,", 1952-1957 (Box 66, Folder 1601)
  - Shaw, Charles B., general correspondence, 1949-1958 (Box 66, Folder 1602)
  - Shaw, Charles B., "American Essays,", 1946-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1603)
  - Shaw, Charles B., "American Essays" (new expanded ed.), 1954-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1604)
  - Shaw, George Bernard, "One Act Plays,", 1956-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1605)
  - Shaw, Irwin, "Lucy Crown,", 1950-1959 (Box 66, Folder 1606)
  - Shaw, Irwin, "Tip on a Dead Jockey,", 1957-1959 (Box 66, Folder 1607)
  - Shaw, Irwin, "The Troubled Air,", 1950-1955 (Box 66, Folder 1608)
  - Shaw, Irwin, "Two Weeks in Another Town,", 1960 (Box 66, Folder 1609)
  - Shaw, Irwin, "The Young Lions,", 1950-1958 (Box 66, Folder 1610)
  - Sheckley, Robert, "The Status Civilization,", 1959-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1611)
  - Sheean, Vincent, "Lily,", 1953-1955 (Box 66, Folder 1612)
  - Sheean, Vincent, "Rage of the Soul,", 1952-1954 (Box 66, Folder 1613)
  - Sherman, Susan, "Give Me Myself,", 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1614)
  - (same as above), undated (Box 66, Folder 1615)
  - Shipley, Clarke, general correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1616)
  - Shirer, William L., "Midcentury Journey,", 1961 (Box 66, Folder 1617)
  - Shirer, William L., "The Rise and Fall of the Third Reich,", 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1618)
  - Shirreffs, Gordon D., "Last Train From Gun Hill,", 1958-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1619)
  - Sholokhov, Mikhail, "And Quiet Flows the Don,", 1959-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1620)
  - Sholokhov, Mikhail, "The Don Flows Home to the Sea,", 1959 (Box 66, Folder 1621)
  - Showers, Paul, "Fortune Telling for Fun and Popularity,", 1954-1958 (Box 66, Folder 1622)
  - Shub, David, "Lenin,", 1950-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1623)
  - Shute, Nevil, "On the Beach,", 1957-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1624)
  - Shute, Nevil, "The Rainbow and the Rose,", 1958-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1625)
  - Shute, Nevil, "Trustee From the Toolroom,", 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1626)
  - Sichel, Pierre, "The Sapbucket Genius,", 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1627)
  - Sillitoe, Alan, "The Loneliness of the Long Distance Runner,", 1959-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1628)
  - Sillitoe, Alan, "Saturday Night and Sunday Morning,", 1959-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1629)
  - Silone, Ignazio, "Bread and Wine,", 1946-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1630)
  - Simcoe, Ben, "A Night Full of Sun,", 1960-1961 (Box 66, Folder 1631)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), general correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 66, Folder 1632)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), general correspondence, 1953 (Box 66, Folder 1633)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), general correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 66, Folder 1634)
  - Simenon, Georges, "Act of Passion,", 1951-1953 (Box 66, Folder 1635)
  - Simenon, Georges, "Belle,", 1952-1954 (Box 66, Folder 1636)
  - Simenon, Georges, "The Bottom of the Bottle,", 1953-1955 (Box 66, Folder 1637)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), "The Brothers Rico,", 1953-1954 (Box 66, Folder 1638)
  - Simenon, Georges, "4 Days in a Lifetime,", 1952-1953 (Box 66, Folder 1639)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), "The Fugitive,", 1954-1958 (Box 66, Folder 1640)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), "The Girl in His Past,", 1951-1952 (Box 66, Folder 1641)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), "Heart of a Man,", 1951-1953 (Box 66, Folder 1642)
  - Simenon, Georges, "The Hitchhiker,", 1955-1957 (Box 66, Folder 1643)
  - Simenon, Georges, "Inspector Maigret and the Killers,", 1955-1956 (Box 66, Folder 1644)
  - Simenon, Georges, "Inspector Maigret and the New York Underworld,", 1953-1956 (Box 66, Folder 1645)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), "I Take This Woman,", 1951-1953 (Box 67, Folder 1646)
  - Simenon, Georges, "Maigret and the Strangled Stripper,", 1953-1955 (Box 67, Folder 1647)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), "No Vacation for Maigret,", 1953-1954 (Box 67, Folder 1648)
  - Simenon, Georges "The Snow Was Black,", 1950-1956 (Box 67, Folder 1649)
  - Simenon, Georges, "Strangers in the House,", 1954-1957 (Box 67, Folder 1650)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), Victor Kosta (pseud.), 1953 (Box 67, Folder 1651)
  - Simenon, Georges (Simenon, Denise), reports, statistics, schedules, censorship, etc., 1951-1956 (Box 67, Folder 1652)
  - Simenon, Georges, press information, undated (Box 67, Folder 1653)
  - Simpson, George Gaylord, "The Meaning of Evolution,", 1950-1960 (Box 67, Folder 1654)
  - Sinclair, Upton, "The Jungle,", 1960-1961 (Box 67, Folder 1655)
  - Siodmak, Curt, "Skyport,", 1959-1961 (Box 67, Folder 1656)
  - Siodmak, Curt, "Svanholm USA,", 1960 (Box 67, Folder 1657)
  - Sirlingo, Charles A.., "A Texas Cowboy,", 1950-1955 (Box 67, Folder 1658)
  - Sklar, George, "The Housewarming,", 1952-1956 (Box 67, Folder 1659)
  - Sklar, George, "The Promising Young Men,", 1951-1957 (Box 67, Folder 1660)
  - Slade, Caroline, general correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 67, Folder 1661)
  - Slade, Caroline, "Lilly Crackell,", 1950-1953 (Box 67, Folder 1662)
  - Slade, Caroline, "Margaret,", 1949-1955 (Box 67, Folder 1663)
  - Slade, Caroline, "The Triumph of Willie Pond,", 1949-1955 (Box 67, Folder 1664)
  - Slater, Humphrey, "Soldiers Three,", 1957-1958 (Box 68.1, Folder 1665)
  - Slaughter, Frank, general correspondence, 1948-1958 (Box 68.1, Folder 1666)
  - Slaughter, Frank, "The Stubborn Heart,", 1950-1960 (Box 68.1, Folder 1667)
  - Slaughter, Frank, "Your Body and Your Mind,", 1948-1958 (Box 68.1, Folder 1668)
  - Slonim, Marc, "An Outline of Russian Literature,", 1958-1960 (Box 68.1, Folder 1669)
  - Slonim, Marc, and Harvey Breit, "This Thing Called Love,", 1954-1958 (Box 68.1, Folder 1670)
  - Small, Peter, "Ocean,", 1960 (Box 68.1, Folder 1671)
  - Smith, Frank, "Harry Vernon at Prep,", 1959-1960 (Box 68.1, Folder 1672)
  - Smith, Huston, "The Religions of Man,", 1957-1961 (Box 68.1, Folder 1673)
  - Smith, Lillian, "Strange Fruit,", 1946-1961 (Box 68.1, Folder 1674)
  - Smith, T.V., general correspondence, 1953-1957 (Box 68.1, Folder 1675)
  - Smith, T.V., "The Democratic Way of Life,", 1948-1952 (Box 68.1, Folder 1676)
  - Smith, T.V., "The Democratic Way of Life,", 1953-1960 (Box 68.1, Folder 1677)
  - Smith, T.V., "The Democratic Way of Life,", 1949-1954 (Box 68.1, Folder 1678)
  - Smith, T.V., "Live Without Fear,", 1954-1961 (Box 68.1, Folder 1679)
  - Smith, T.V., "On Living With Your Problems,", 1953-1955 (Box 68.1, Folder 1680)
  - Smith, Wilfred Cantwell, "Islam,", 1952-1961 (Box 68.1, Folder 1681)
  - Smith, William G., general correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 68.2, Folder 1682)
  - Smith, William Gardner, "Anger at Innocence,", 1950-1955 (Box 68.2, Folder 1683)
  - Smith, Z.Z., "This Time Next Year,", 1961 (Box 68.2, Folder 1684)
  - Smith, Z.Z., "Until One of Us is Dead,", 1960-1961 (Box 68.2, Folder 1685)
  - Smollet, Tobias, "Humphrey Clinker,", 1959-1960 (Box 68.2, Folder 1686)
  - Sneider, Vern, "The King from Ashtabula,", 1960-1961 (Box 68.2, Folder 1687)
  - Sneider, Vern, "A Long Way From Home,", 1957-1960 (Box 68.2, Folder 1688)
  - Sneider, Vern, "Teahouse of the August Moon,", 1955-1960 (Box 68.2, Folder 1689)
  - Snow, C.P., "The Search,", 1958-1960 (Box 68.2, Folder 1690)
  - Snow, C.P., "Science and Government,", 1961 (Box 68.2, Folder 1691)
  - Snow, C.P., "The Two Cultures and the Scientific Revolution,", 1960-1961 (Box 68.2, Folder 1692)
  - Soule, George, "Ideas of the Great Economists,", 1953-1960 (Box 68.2, Folder 1693)
  - Soule, George, "Introduction to Economic Science,", 1948-1959 (Box 68.2, Folder 1694)
  - Soule, George, "Men, Wages, and Employment,", 1950-1957 (Box 68.2, Folder 1695)
  - Soule, George, "The Shape of Tomorrow,", 1954-1958 (Box 68.2, Folder 1696)
  - Soule, George, "Twentieth Century Fund,", 1949-1954 (Box 68.2, Folder 1697)
  - Sourian, Peter, "Miri,", 1957-1959 (Box 68.2, Folder 1698)
  - Spender, Stephen, "Goethe,", 1955-1961 (Box 68.2, Folder 1699)
  - Spillane, Mickey, general correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 68.2, Folder 1700)
  - Spillane, Mickey, general correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 68.2, Folder 1701)
  - Spillane, Mickey, general correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 68.3, Folder 1702)
  - Spillane, Mickey, general correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 68.3, Folder 1703)
  - Spillane, Mickey, "The Big Kill,", 1951-1960 (Box 68.3, Folder 1704)
  - Spillane, Mickey, "The Deep,", 1961 (Box 68.3, Folder 1705)
  - Spillane, Mickey, "I, the Jury,", 1948-1959 (Box 68.3, Folder 1706)
  - Spillane, Mickey, "Kiss Me Deadly,", 1952-1960 (Box 68.3, Folder 1707)
  - Spillane, Mickey, "The Long Wait,", 1950-1960 (Box 68.3, Folder 1708)
  - Spillane, Mickey, "My Gun is Quick,", 1949-1959 (Box 68.3, Folder 1709)
  - Spillane, Mickey, "One Lonely Night,", 1950-1960 (Box 68.3, Folder 1710)
  - Spillane, Mickey, "Vengeance is Mine,", 1950-1960 (Box 68.3, Folder 1711)
  - Spiller, Robert, "The Cycle of American Literature,", 1950-1962 (Box 68.3, Folder 1712)
  - Spota, Luis, "The Wounds of Hunger,", 1957-1959 (Box 69 A., Folder 1713)
  - Stace, Walter, "Mysticism,", 1959-1961 (Box 69 A., Folder 1714)
  - Stadley, Pat, "The Black Leather Barbarians,", 1958-1961 (Box 69 A., Folder 1715)
  - Stadley, Pat, "Run, Copper, Run,", 1958-1959 (Box 69 A., Folder 1716)
  - Starkie, Walter, general correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 69 A., Folder 1717)
  - Starkie, Walter, "Don Quixote,", 1957-1961 (Box 69 A., Folder 1718)
  - Starkie, Walter, "Exemplary Novels,", 1961 (Box 69 A., Folder 1719)
  - Stearns, Marshall, "The Story of Jazz,", 1958-1960 (Box 69 A., Folder 1720)
  - Stefferud, Alfred, general correspondence, 1951-1958 (Box 69 A., Folder 1721)
  - Stefferud, Alfred, "How to Know the Wildflowers,", 1948-1949 (Box 69 A., Folder 1722)
  - Stefferud, Alfred, "How to Know the Wildflowers,", 1950-1958 (Box 69 A., Folder 1723)
  - Stefferud, Alfred, "The Wonderful World of Books,", 1952 (Box 69 B., Folder 1724)
  - Stefferud, Alfred, "The Wonderful World of Books,", 1953 (Box 69 B., Folder 1725)
  - Stefferud, Alfred, "The Wonderful World of Books,"1954-61, 1954-1961 (Box 69 B., Folder 1726)
  - Stefferud, Alfred, "The Wonderful World of Books," outlines, correspondence, circular letters, promotion, undated (Box 69 B., Folder 1727)
  - Stefferud, Alfred, "The Wonderful World of Books," promotional materials, ms., undated (Box 69 B., Folder 1728)
  - Steinbeck, John, "Tortilla Flat,", 1946-1959 (Box 69 B., Folder 1729)
  - Steinberg, Saul, "All in Line,", 1946-1959 (Box 69 B., Folder 1730)
  - Stephens, James, "Dierdre,", 1961 (Box 69 B., Folder 1731)
  - Stern, Jill, "Nine Miles to Reno" ["Not in Our Stars"], 1956-1958 (Box 69 B., Folder 1732)
  - Stern, Philip Van Doren, "Love is the One With Wings,", 1949-1955 (Box 69 C., Folder 1733)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis, "Kidnapped,", 1959-1962 (Box 69 C., Folder 1734)
  - Stewart, Desmond, "Leopard in the Grass,", 1951-1954 (Box 69 C., Folder 1735)
  - Stewart, Desmond, "A Stranger in Eden,", 1952-1957 (Box 69 C., Folder 1736)
  - Stokes, Donald, "Appointment With Fear,", 1950-1952 (Box 69 C., Folder 1737)
  - Stokes, Donald, "Captive in the Night,", 1950-1955 (Box 69 C., Folder 1738)
  - Stone, Andrew, general correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 69 C., Folder 1739)
  - Stone, Andrew, "Cry Terror,", 1957-1961 (Box 69 C., Folder 1740)
  - Stone, Andrew, "Decks Ran Red,", 1958-1961 (Box 69 C., Folder 1741)
  - Stone, Andrew, "Julie,", 1956-1957 (Box 69 C., Folder 1742)
  - Stone, Irving, "The Agony and the Ecstasy,", 1961 (Box 69 C., Folder 1743)
  - Stone, John A., "The Sufferings of Young Werther,", 1960 (Box 69 C., Folder 1744)
  - Strong, Philip, "State Fair,", 1950-1960 (Box 69 C., Folder 1745)
  - Storer, John, "The Web of Life,", 1953-1961 (Box 69 C., Folder 1746)
  - Styron, William, general correspondence, 1952-1961 (Box 69 C., Folder 1747)
  - Styron, William, "Lie Down in Darkness,", 1951-1960 (Box 69 C., Folder 1748)
  - Styron, William, "Set This House on Fire,", 1959-1961 (Box 69 C., Folder 1749)
  - Suggs, Robert, "Children of Tangeroa,", 1959-1961 (Box 69 C., Folder 1750)
  - Suggs, Robert, "An Expedition to the Marquesas Islands,", 1960-1961 (Box 69 C., Folder 1751)
  - Sullivan, J.W.N., "Beethoven,", 1946-1958 (Box 70, Folder 1752)